Your opinion, what are the best three industries that
people should be looking to get into in order
to create wealth in today's world? Number one,
I would say real estate. It's such a fantastic
market to get into, and you can get in
relatively inexpensively and do that by yourself. Number two,
technology, but unfortunately, you really need to know
a lot about technology as it relates to
which technology is going to propel your wealth
versus maybe suck your wealth. There are a lot
of great technology ideas out there, and then
there are even more terrible ones. So really
being able to figure out the difference
is critical. Number three, an industry that you
know something about. That's always something I
would recommend, and whether it's a little
bit or a lot, make sure you
get into something that you're already familiar with.